

Contacts

+380-093-594-1984

sirov@ukr.net

Telegram

GitHub

Linkedin

Nosivka, Ukraine

Tech Skills

- HTML5
- CSS
- PHP
- MySQL
- JavaScript
- SASS
- TypeScript
- React
- Redux
- **REST API**
- Laravel
- Node.js

Soft Skills

- Critical thinking
- Time management
- Problem-solving
- Communication
- Creativity

Languages

- Ukrainian native
- Russian upper-intermediate
- English upper-intermediate

Oleh Syrovatko Junior Full Stack developer

Summary

With over 10 years of experience as a full-stack developer, including working on a large-scale social ped project, I am excited to pursue a role as a Junior Front-End Developer. I have successfully contributed to the creation of a popular social network for Ukrainian settlements, which attracted 583K unique visitors last year. I am confident that my skills, passion and experience in building user-centric applications will enable me to make valuable contributions to your company.

Project Experience

lua.com.ua (HTML, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL, Laravel)

First social network about all Ukrainian settlements. Contain more than 1 million photos and 115k users organized by Laravel Framework. Role: Team lead. Individual project.

afc.cn.ua, GitHub (HTML, SAAS, CSS, JS, PHP, MySQL)

It's a little project about some building company. Several pages introduse products, projects, feedback, contacts and admin panel. Role: Team lead. Individual project.

MIMIHO, GitHub (HTML, SASS, JS, Parce)

It's a small project about restaurant. All the pages mobile adapted, have excelent performance, accessibility.

Role: Team lead. Group project.

Movies, GitHub Front GitHub Back (TypeScript React Node.js MongoDB)

A movie site, connected to a backend API. Users can register, log in, view, search, add, and remove favorite movies, and manage bookmarks. Role: Developer. Individual project

Work Experience

Chief Accountant

PF Sa-Ha Trans 2016-2024

- Accounting: Financial record-keeping and compliance
- International Logistics: Managing global shipments and deliveries
- Finance: Financial operations oversight and analysis

Achieving an increase in the company's profitability and an increase in its capital more than 30%.

Full Stack Developer

First allukrainian social network 2006-present

- full development lifecycle, including concept-to-deployment
- ensuring best practices and quality standards
- conducting code reviews, provide code quality and maintainability
- implementing scalable database structures
- handling large volumes of photos and user data

Achievement: 583K unique visitors per last year.

Education

2022 - 2023IT School GoIT, Fullstack Developer

2000 - 2005Kyiv National Economic University, Master of accounting,

analysis and auditing